<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FACTOR on Kusumoto&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://kusumotonorio.github.io/categories/FACTOR.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in FACTOR on Kusumoto&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-jp</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kusumotonorio.github.io/categories/FACTOR/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Factor Inline Input 3</title>
      <link>https://kusumotonorio.github.io/2019/05/inline-input-3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kusumotonorio.github.io/2019/05/inline-input-3.html</guid>
      <description>It is now possible to display underlines during inline Japanese conversion. I have made several other improvements and believe that I have achieved my goal.
Click the image above to see a video of the conversion and input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factor Inline Input 2</title>
      <link>https://kusumotonorio.github.io/2019/04/inline-input-2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kusumotonorio.github.io/2019/04/inline-input-2.html</guid>
      <description>The inline input/conversion has become stable because I understood the cause of the crash of Factor IDE.
Click this image to see a video of the conversion.
I have made progress towards completion, but the current implementation lacks a very large one.
Inline conversion uses the underline display to tell the user the target area of the conversion operation and the break of the conversion unit. For now, there is no such feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factor Inline Input 1</title>
      <link>https://kusumotonorio.github.io/2019/04/inline-input-1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kusumotonorio.github.io/2019/04/inline-input-1.html</guid>
      <description>I want to make Factor inline input possible with CJK languages such as Japanese. So, I&amp;rsquo;m modifying it. However, I&amp;rsquo;ve got stuck.
For example, I use the return key to confirm the conversion string, but I can not operate well because the key input to IM such as return passes over to Factor.
I expected the key input to be received first by the IM, and the app received the input that was not consumed, but it seems that the IM can&amp;rsquo;t receive the input unless the Factor backend sends a key-down event.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
